Q1-3
1 Do you have a hard time making informed budget decisions
regarding your small business?
Is it difficult to track your company's profits and losses?
2 FS Tracker Pro is an easy-to-use software program
especially designed to help small business owners record income,
expenditures, and other important accounting information.
You can then create customized reports
to share with your clients or financial advisors.
3 Call us today at 555-0132.
One of our experienced representatives will gladly arrange an office visit
to show you just how easy the FS Tracker Pro is to use.
We're sure you'll be impressed!
Q4-6
4 Hi, I'm Doctor Rajesh Sharma,
chief eye surgeon at the new Meadowbrook Laser Vision Correction Center.
Our center has just opened at 4 Lombard Street,
next to the Townsend Supermarket.
You may be asking, "Why choose one of our doctors?"
5 Because we've performed thousands of vision correction procedures
- many more than any other surgeons in the area.
If you have a vision problem,
our computerized laser surgery may be able to help.
6 We're offering a free consultation to our first one hundred customers,
so act now!
Come in and see us today!
Q7-9
7,8 Tonight, world famous chef Emily Cho
will open the doors to her newest venture: Tiara's.
Come and enjoy authentic and flavorful Italian dishes
in a fun and relaxing atmosphere that overlooks the city skyline.
Unlike some of Ms. Cho's other renowned restaurants,
Tiara's has been specifically designed for families
and offers a special children's menu.
Join us for our opening tonight
- 9 just call 555-0842 to reserve a table for your family,
and experience the very best at Tiara's.
Q10-12
No time to eat?
Need a burst of energy?
Look no further!
The German consumer goods company that brought you Brainy Grains Cereal
is now offering a new product.
10 EZ Yum is a wholesome treat that will help you feel full and satisﬁed.
11 It is high in fiber, low in fat and packed with protein.
This healthy snack is a great alternative to junk food.
You won't be able to get enough!
12 EZ Yum is available in most grocery stores, so head to the nearest one today!
Q13-15
Here's a special offer from 13 Lifeline Electronics.
Everyone knows that Lifeline Electronics has the lowest prices in the area.
But 14 now through Friday, prices are even lower on our complete line of digital cameras.
That's right! All of our digital cameras are fifteen percent off their usual low prices!
14 Remember, this special offer ends Friday, so hurry!
And when you buy your new camera, 15 don't forget to ask for one of our complimentary camera bags.
Come visit Lifeline Electronics today!
We're conveniently located in the Springdale Shopping Center, just off Highway 65.
Q16-18
16 Are you thinking about getting a degree in business?
Then Hamson College, the school for business management, is for you.
Our specialized courses focus on all aspects of running your own company.
With both on-site and online courses,
Hamson College offers courses that can ﬁt into anyone's schedule.
17 In fact, Hamson was ranked by students as having the most scheduling flexibility of any college.
18 Come to an information session on August seventeenth to ﬁnd out if Hamson College is right for you.
You'll be able to meet with professors and talk with other students.
To ﬁnd out more, visit us at www.hamsoncollege.edu.
Q19-21
Come to Katsuo'sTennis Club and perfect your forehand and backhand swings with tennis pro Katsuo Fujimoto.
19 Mr. Fujimoto has twenty years of instruction experience and is famous for winning multiple tennis championships,
so beginning to advanced students can learn something valuable from him.
And 21 with our newly expanded pro shop, with an even larger selection of tennis rackets and clothes,
you can find something valuable to play with, too!
Make sure to look in the Salt City Shopping Magazine to find special discount coupons
like 20 buy-one get-one-free lessons for kids, half-priced adult classes,
or free guest passes for members on the weekend.
So get off the bleachers and onto the courts today!